<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on me, jannik</title>
    <link>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on me, jannik</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 12:21:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Exhalation</title>
      <link>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/exhalation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/exhalation/</guid>
      <description>Exhalation by Ted Ciang  Will make you think, grapple with big questions, and feel more human. The best kind of science fiction. - Barack Obama
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Factfulness</title>
      <link>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/factfulness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 01:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/factfulness/</guid>
      <description>Factfulness by Hans Rosling  &amp;lsquo;A hopeful book about the potential for human progress when we work off facts rather than our inherent biases.&amp;rsquo; - Barack Obama
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daring Greatly</title>
      <link>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/daring_greatly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/daring_greatly/</guid>
      <description>Daring Greatly by Brené Brown How the Courage to Be Vulnerable Transforms the Way We Live, Love, Parent, and Lead
 What I find remarkable about this book is the unique combination of solid research and kitchen table story-telling. Brené becomes such a real person in the book that you can actually hear her voice asking, &amp;ldquo;Have you dared greatly today?&amp;rdquo; The invitation in this book is clear: We must be larger than anxiety, fear, and shame if we want to speak, act, and show up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inferior</title>
      <link>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/inferior/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/inferior/</guid>
      <description>Inferior by Angela Saini How science got women wrong - and the new research that&amp;rsquo;s rewriting the story
 This is an important book that I hope will be widely read. Any time biases are identified and corrected for, it is science and policymaking rather than feminism or any particular ideology that comes out ahead. — Sarah Blaffer Hrdy
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We are the Weather</title>
      <link>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/we_are_the_weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/we_are_the_weather/</guid>
      <description>We are the Weather by Jonathan Safran Foer Saving the planet begins at breakfast.
 Eye-opening&amp;hellip; In this follow-up to his influential Eating Animals, [Foer] brings both personality and passion to an issue that no one has figured out how to address in a way that inspires an adequate response. - The New York Times Book Review
 This book is on my to read list!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Behave</title>
      <link>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/behave/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/behave/</guid>
      <description>Behave by Robert Sapolsky The biology of Humans at our best and worst. Great to get a perspective of how many factors influence us to act in certain ways.
 Have you actually read the whole book? I don&amp;rsquo;t think anyone has. - a friend
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawdown</title>
      <link>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/drawdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/drawdown/</guid>
      <description>Drawdown by Paul Hawken Drawdown describes the 100 most substantive solutions to global warming.
 Drawdown is an exceptional example of cooperation between some of the sharpest thinkers on climate and energy matters, an atlas that has the potential to save the planet. — Andreas Kuhlmann, CEO German Energy Agency
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sapiens</title>
      <link>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/sapiens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janniktheyssen.github.io/books/sapiens/</guid>
      <description>Sapiens by Yuval Noah Harari  Interesting and provocative&amp;hellip; It gives you a sense of perspective on how briefly we’ve been on this earth, how short things like agriculture and science have been around, and why it makes sense for us to not take them for granted. - Barack Obama
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>